She was as strong as the land for which she fought.  And as vulnerable.
Comes a Horseman is a western, drama, romance film directed by Alan J. Pakula.
Ella Connors is a single woman who gets pressured to sell her failing
cattle farm to her corrupt ex-suitor, Jacob Ewing.
She asks for help from her neighbor, Frank Athearn.
As Ella and Frank fight back through stampedes,
jealousy, betrayal, and sabotage...
they eventually find love.
Frank 'Buck' Athearn, played by James Caan.
Ella Connors, played by Jane Fonda.
Jacob 'J.W.' Ewing, played by Jason Robards.
Neil Atkinson, played by George Grizzard.
Dodger, played by Richard Farnsworth.
Billy Joe Meynert, played by Mark Harmon.
Comes a Horseman is a 1978 American Western drama film starring Jane Fonda, James
Caan, Jason Robards, and Richard Farnsworth, directed by Alan J.
Set in the American West of the 1940s but not a typical Western, it tells the story of two ranchers, Frank "Buck" Athearn (Caan) and Ella Conners (Fonda),
whose small operation is threatened both by economic hardship and the expansionist dreams of local land baron Jacob "J.W." Ewing (Robards).
The film explores themes of cattle drive, oil, oil
industry, neo-western, cattle baron.
The tone is emotional.